

F LPT · CYBER SECURITY ENGINEER

 +91 (981) 773-6245
 | ■ kunaljaglan14@gmail.com
 | ■ github.com/hoodietramp
 | ■ linkedin.com/in/h00dy

Who am I?

An experienced CyberSecurity Engineer with over 2 years of experience in Network Pentesting and Cyber Security forward mindset.

I hold an **eJPTv2 certificate** and **CNPen by SecOps Group**, pursuing a Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science with specialization in cloud technology and information security. With each keystroke, I strive further to the Dark Arts of Computing, devoting the better part of my life oscillating between Individual Contribution and maintaining a versatile skillset spanning the breadth of contemporary security practices, from to **AppSec** to **NetSec** to **DevSecOps**, with a firm emphasis on **OffSec** ensuring the ethos of hacking space and cyber world remain in me so that i may never lose sight of its inherent struggles.

- I am my own worst critic. As a result, I allow myself the space to navigate burnouts and re-writing internet privacy rights when they're still left, and recently, probing the whimsy of the **IoT Sphere**, all from the comfort of my cubicle.

Work Experience _____

Panipat Institute Of Engineering And Technology

Panipat, India

CyberSecurity Club Lead

Apr 2023 - Present

- · Coordinated and conducted knowledge-sharing sessions, actively mentoring junior team members to enhance their skills.
- · Proudly organized a CTF event at PIET
- **@** @h4ckp13t

TryHackMe UK, Remote

CTF Player May 2022 - Present

- · Practice vulnerable machines and labs based on Linux / Windows OS for online penetration testing.
- · Currently engaged in the development of vulnerable machines and labs based on Linux OS for online penetration testing.
- THM-Profile | h00dy

HackTheBoxUK, Remote

CTF Player May 2022 - Present

- Actively engage in penetration testing activities on the HTB platform, practicing machines to exploit the latest CVEs and enhance my skills.
- Completed various challenges and achieved a ranking of Hacker on the HTB platform.
- Regularly participate in Capture The Flag (CTF) competitions hosted on HTB, demonstrating problem-solving and cybersecurity skills.
- O HTB-Profile | h00dy

H4ckp13T CTFCapture the flag

https://instagram.com/h4ckp13t

April 2023

• Hosted and handled college cybersecurity event (H4ckp13T CTF).

Projects.

capNcook

https://github.com/hoodietramp/capNcook

November 2023

- This is a python flask based web application to search over tor and grab response codes / TOR whois info / response headers / screenshots / subdirectories of onion web-servers.
- Identification of entry and exit nodes, ensuring anonymity and privacy when interacting with onion domains, including circuit rebuilding to maintain security.
- Based on efficient multi-threading in python.

Achievements & Certifications _____

2022	First Place, Smart Punjab Hackathon 2022	Saturnalia, Thapar
2023	eJPT v2, eLearn Junior Pentester Certification	eLearn Security
2024	CNPen, Certified Network Pentester (CNPen)	The SecOps Group
2022	Top 1% WorldWide , TryHackMe Top 3 in monthly country leaderboards	TryHackMe.com

Education

APRIL 28, 2024

Panipat Institute Of Engineering And Technology

Panipat, India

BCA Cloud Technology And Information Security(CT & IS)

May 2022 - Current

• Current GPA: 72%, Studying CyberSecurity with both focus and passion, implementing the knowledge of TCP/IP protocols, python programming and Linux handling, and working on multiple side applications and scripts

Sky Hawk International School

Delhi, India

April 2020 - July 2021

• Specialised in Physics, Chemistry, and Biology

Skills

High School

Programming Python, PHP, C/C++, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Java, SQL, Go.

Miscellaneous Amazon S3 Buckets, Linux, Shell (Bash/Zsh), Regex, OWASP TOP 10, Docker, Vagrant, Git.

APRIL 28, 2024 2